nevadaart.org 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Nevada Museum of Art

The Nevada Museum of Art is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website, shop at the Museum Store online, or use the website to purchase a Museum membership or make an online donation. The Museum does not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless the individual visiting the Museum website knowingly provides it. By using the Museum website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Museum’s Privacy Policy. The Museum Privacy Policy is outlined below.

### The Nevada Museum of Art policy on collecting information on the Museum website

#### Online Purchases

When you order a product from the Museum Store online, we need to know your name, billing and shipping addresses, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information to process your order. Your credit card information will be used only as needed to process your transaction.

#### Online Memberships and Donations

When you purchase a Museum membership or make a donation to the Museum online, we will ask you to provide us with the information we need to process your membership and/or to acknowledge your contribution. This information includes your name, billing and shipping addresses, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information. Your credit card information will be used only as needed to process your transaction.

#### Children Twelve and Under

The Museum does not solicit personal information from children. Visitors twelve years of age and under should remember that they are required to obtain an adult’s permission before submitting any personal information to this or any other website.

#### Nevada Museum of Art E-Newsletter

As a service, the Museum offers visitors to the Museum website the opportunity to subscribe to one or more of our online newsletters, a service hosted by a contractor that has agreed to use the e-mail address you provide only to send e-newsletters to you. If you choose to subscribe, you will receive the Museum e-newsletters on the topics you choose. You may subscribe or unsubscribe at any time by following the e-newsletter instructions.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small files of information that are stored on your computer’s hard drive by your Web browser. The cookies we use do not contain any personal information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change the preferences of your browser so that it does not accept them. In order to use all the features of the Museum Store online, we recommend that you accept cookies.

#### The Nevada Museum of Art policy on the use and disclosure of the information it collects on the Museum website

The Museum uses the personal information you provide to us for internal purposes, such as filling and tracking your order, analyzing trends and collecting statistics.

The Museum will not disclose or share any personal information you provide to the Museum with any other party without your permission, except if requested to do so in accordance with a court order, subpoena, or similar legal order, and in the event such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of the Museum, its users, and other third parties. The Museum will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

We may combine information you give to us online, in our stores or at the Museum. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about products or events that may be of interest to you, or for other promotional purposes.

#### Linking

The Museum Website may include links to websites operated by third parties over which we have no control. Once you leave the Museum website, the Museum Privacy Policy will not apply, and you access such sites at your own risk.

#### Security

The Museum secure server software uses industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. SSL encodes your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, as it travels over the Internet so that all transactions are secure. If you prefer, you may also place a Museum Store order by phone at 775.329.3333 ex.107 or by fax at 775.329.1541. For membership gifts, please call 775.329.3333 and for donations, please call 775.329.3333 ex.232.

#### Revisions to our Privacy Policy

Please note that the Museum may revise its privacy policy at any time, without notice, with such changes to be effective immediately upon posting on the Museum website. Such revisions may arise in response to changes in the law, policy, or other factors. We encourage you to periodically visit this page to review our most current policy.

#### Contact the Nevada Museum of Art

Send your questions, comments, or concerns about our privacy policy or any other aspect of our website to the [Communications Department](mailto:art@nevadaart.org)
